# Vitor Correia

# Full-Stack Developer

#### **PROFILE**

I am a +1 year experienced highly motivated web developer, recent graduate at Concordia bootcamp, looking for a new challenge where I can keep learning and add my values as a hard worker who builds confidence and trust at all levels.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## **TAILBASE**

# **Junior Web Developer**

OCT 2019, LAVAL, QC

- Responsible to set up websites for new clients, using ColdFusion,
  CSS (SASS) and SQL, to achieve at least 15 launches per month.
- Help the support team to make changes to websites according to customer requests, reducing the response time.
- Add new features, make changes to the models and deploy them, respecting the tasks assigned to me in the sprint meetings.
- Manage tickets at JIRA/DevOps, always respecting the delivery time.
- Daily agile meeting.

## **QA Analyst**

NOV 2018 - OCT 2019, LAVAL, QC

- Assessing and test user interface (UI) new websites functionalities, to increase sales and reduce further support tickets.
- Identify and document bugs to developers through JIRA tool.
- Follow opened tickets progress.

## **Data Entry Clerk**

OCT 2018 - OCT 2019, LAVAL, QC

- Update and register appliances.
- Verify the accuracy of data.
- Edit and upload product images.
- Reply to internal and external customers.

vitorbaziliogcorreia@gmail.com 438-926-4546 linkedin.com/in/vitor-correia github.com/vitor-correia10

#### **SKILLS**

HTML/CSS (SASS), JavaScript, React, Redux, Node, ColdFusion, SQL, MongoDB, GitHub and Agile methodology

#### **LANGUAGE**

**English and Portuguese** 

#### **INTEREST**

Programming, travel and sports

**Achievement:** Made a spreadsheet with some NGO and government's programs that help small and medium companies with employee costs, thus being able to reduce the costs of some employees by up to 75%.

## **RETRIGO**

# **Operations Director**

OCT 2016 - OCT 2018, MONTREAL, QC

- One of those responsible for thinking and planning new ideas with a focus on the continuous improvement of our application.
- Test and report issues to developers and follow the results.
- Manage and report website statistics to maximize the return on our resources.
- Manage a team of 5 people.
- Daily agile meeting.

**Achievement:** Registered more than 200 retreats in 3 months on the website.

#### **EDUCATION**

# **Concordia University | Full-Stack Web Development**

MAR 2020 - NOV 2020, MONTREAL, QC

- Front-end: JavaScript, React, Redux, HTML/CSS.
- Back-end: Node.js, Express, MongoDB.
- Tools: Git & GitHub.

# **Gama Filho University | Bachelor of Business Administration**

JAN 2008 - DEC 2012, BRAZIL

#### **VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE**

## **BRASA**

# **Quebec Membership Coordinator**

JAN 2018 – OCT 2018, MONTREAL, QC

- Promote BRASA Canada on universities/colleges in Quebec.
- Provide support for creating BRASA account.
- Support recruitment of ambassadors.
- Disclose BRASA and BRASA Canada's campaigns.
- Manage BRASA meetings in Montreal.